T. J. Anderson Papers MS006
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Additional accessions, 1928 -- 2012; 1928 -- 2010; MS006.006; 46.8 Linear Feet; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Graduale Sanctae Ambianensis Ecclesiae, MS006.006.073 (Box data_value_missing_961a48145ce75bb447e291fcb6650ed5, Box 73)
    Leather and wood-bound volume of religious music in Latin circa mid-1700s.
  - Scores, MS006.006.074 (Box data_value_missing_bfc0175763a9ea7d44b13bcf562ece38, Box 74)
  - Scores, MS006.006.075 (Box data_value_missing_bfc0175763a9ea7d44b13bcf562ece38, Box 75)
  - Scores, MS006.006.076 (Box data_value_missing_bfc0175763a9ea7d44b13bcf562ece38, Box 76)
  - Scores, MS006.006.077 (Box data_value_missing_bfc0175763a9ea7d44b13bcf562ece38, Box 77)
  - Scores, MS006.006.078 (Box data_value_missing_bfc0175763a9ea7d44b13bcf562ece38, Box 78)
  - Scores, MS006.006.079 (Box data_value_missing_bfc0175763a9ea7d44b13bcf562ece38, Box 79)
  - Scores, MS006.006.080 (Box data_value_missing_bfc0175763a9ea7d44b13bcf562ece38, Box 80)
  - Scores, MS006.006.081 (Box data_value_missing_bfc0175763a9ea7d44b13bcf562ece38, Box 81)
  - Honorary degree hoods, MS006.006.082 (Box data_value_missing_961a48145ce75bb447e291fcb6650ed5, Box 82)
  - Baby book, diplomas, and "A Birthday Offering to TJ Anderson", 1928 -- 1978; MS006.006.083 (Box data_value_missing_464b2eedf7bede247ed3c50e1ce5ff59, Box 83)
    Baby book, 1928; high school diploma, 1946; college diploma, 1950; "A Birthday Offering to TJ Anderson" compilation of letters and music presented to Anderson on his 50th birthday, 1978.
- Website, 2012-2019; MS006.007; 1 Web sites
  This series is open for research.
  Website crawled by DCA to document the presence of T. J. Anderson on the web. The website in this series is crawled on an annual basis.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Archived websites can be viewed online using the Internet Archive's Wayback Machine.
  - T.J. Anderson, Composer, 2012-04-09 -- 2019-09-18; MS006.000554; 1 Web sites
- 2019 accessions, 2018 -- 2019; MS006.008
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Gift of T.J. Anderson's daughter Janet, 2019, accession MS-2019-084.
  This series is arranged in received order.
  This series contains a CD recording, a story by T. J. Anderson III, an article from "The Syncopated Times," and an award.
  - "Black Composers Series, 1974 -- 1978", 2018; MS006.000556 (Case 35)
  - "Devonte Travels the Sorry Route," by T. J. Anderson III, 2019; MS006.000557 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Inscribed by the author to his parents.
  - "Blowing off the Dust: Goin' Around with Treemonisha," by Larry Melton, 2019 April; MS006.000558 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    Clipping from "The Syncopated Times."
  - Composers Now Visionary award, 2019; MS006.000559 (Box 84)
    Includes event program and a photograph of Anderson holding the award.